No I wouldn't refer
to any particular people
but I would just
say that this particular
policy I think is
akin to Yeah it's
not well advised
Another issue in this
you could be right
All this technology be
going in the right
direction but economically we
could be towards a
Do you think that's
true Yeah yeah So
I would separate out
the two things One
is the basic exponential
and that's what we've
been talking about That's
been kind of the
technological direction
And there just like
with Moore's law you
can never be sure
that the technology is
sort of fully going
to advance It's gonna
keep going right It's
a fundamentally inductive problem
But now that I've
seen well over a
of it I would
say I am pretty
confident that it's gonna
continue or at least
I'm more confident than
I've ever been at
any time in the